

ABOUT ME

When we're kids everyone wants to be something cool like an astronaut or a fireman, but those desires quickly change as we grow older as our interests change. When I started developing my own musical tastes as a teenager I became obsessed with hip-hop culture. I longed for a career in the rap game, so much so that I started creating album artwork for my imaginary rap career. While I never quite became the next Eminem, I did end up discovering a love for design along the way. What started out as a teenage hobby quickly evolved into a passion as I found myself designing logos, album artwork, and flyers for my more musically talented friends.

Now, 15 years later my passion for design continues. And while I sometimes still fantasize about rocking a stage with a mic in hand, I know I have a stronger eye for design than lyrical prowess. Taking everything I've learned over the years I strive to create visual work that not only looks good, but helps connect your brand to the world.

SKILLS + HOBBIES

- Lavout
- Typography
- Branding
- Photography
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, After Effects
- Basic HTML/CSS
- Kayaking
- Cycling
- Dungeons & Dragons (PC + DM)
- Mini-figure Painting

CONTACT

239.405.9711
ijacksondesign@gmail.com

ianjacksondesign.com

IAN JACKSON

CREATIVE DESIGN + BRANDING

EXPERIENCE

PARR MOTO I GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Fort Myers, FL | 2014-2020

- Producing seasonal retail marketing assets for in-store and online usage for the entire U.S. Harley-Davidson dealership network. These included posters, promo cards, outdoor signage, web banners, emails, animated GIFs, and more
- · Laying out instructional guides detailing marketing best practices
- · Delivering final print files and proofing prints

MUD READY APPAREL | OWNER

Lehigh Acres, FL | 2015-2018

- · Developing brand identity and merchandise
- Designing and maintaining webstore and ensuring inventory is kept up-to-date
- · Creating promotional graphics to be shared on social channels

CUSTOMTEESNOW | PRINT ARTIST

Naples, FL | 2015-2016

- Preparing artwork for screenprinting
- · Creating custom designs for customers that don't have their own artwork
- Communicating with customers about their art and working with them to receive final approval before printing
- · Proofing test prints to ensure proper placement and colors

FGCU ATHLETICS | GRAPHIC DESIGN INTERN

Fort Myers, FL | 2012-2015

- Collaborating with the marketing department to produce game day materials such as event flyers, newspaper ads, social posts, billboards, and schedule cards & magnets
- Developing wall wraps for various facilities around the sports complex
- · Laying out donor sponsorship proposal packages

EDUCATION

FLORIDA GULF COAST UNIVERSITY

Fort Myers, FL | 2011-2015 | Bachelor of Art

UNIVERSITY DESIGN GROUP | PRESIDENT

Fort Myers, FL | 2014-2015